The next thing we are going to do is to add 2 kinds of sugar to our recipe and it is easy to get this right because you just need 1 cup of each.
We will start off with the white sugar which is in a container here and we just want to make sure that it is an even cup of sugar.
You can use the edge of the knife and add that gradually and as that goes in, it will mix with the margarine or in this case, butter, that has been creaming in this mixer bowl.
As it is creaming, you want to take another cup of brown sugar and this happens to be dark brown sugar; I think this gives a nice flavor.
You can also use light brown sugar.
The important thing to remember is that it should be fresh so that it is easily put into the measuring container.
I just stick it right into the bag and with your hand, you can make sure you get an even amount.
This is going to come out in a bit of a clump so I am going to turn it off for a moment and let that go in there and I will use this opportunity to scrape down the sides and the sides of the bowl and also to scrape the beaters so that this will get mixed in.
You see it is getting nice and creamy now and that will continue as the brown sugar and the white sugar become incorporated into the mixture.
It doesn’t need to be at a high speed; just enough so that it will mix nicely.